(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-26T16:31:20.403787",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
おはよう こんにちは こんばんは！
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening!
ERB TVの「Now That's a Bop」へようこそ！
Welcome to ERB TV's "Now That's a Bop"!
司会を務めるのは私…おーっほっほっほ！
I'm your host, ohohoho!
薔薇は紅く、我が心の炎は蒼く燃え上がる
Roses are red, the fire in my heart burns blue,
緋色の女王、そしてJusticeのリーダー！
also known as the Scarlet Queen, the leader of Justice!
エリザベス・ローズ・ブラッドフレムです！
I am Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame!
素敵にお会いできて…すてき…すてき！
Lovely to see you, to see you... Lovely!
会場には熱狂的なロザリアンの皆さんが集まっています！はっざー！
We have an excited crowd of Rosarians here, huzzah!
最高の楽曲を届ける準備万端の素晴らしいクルーたちね！はっざー！
And a great crew ready to bring some awesome tunes to you all, huzzah!
今夜は非常にノリの良い曲をたくさん用意しているわよ
We've got a massive lineup of absolute bops.
今夜の特別なテーマは…「80年代！」
Tonight, we have a special theme: music from the '80s!
お家で楽しんでいる皆さんももし番組が気に入ったらハッシュタグで教えてね
Make sure you folks at home, if you're enjoying the show, let us know using the hashtag...
#ERBday2026 よ！これよ！これ！
#ERBday2026! Right up there, right up there!
OK！それでは最初の1曲目にいきましょう
OK! Let's get started with our first bop.
準備はいい？「フライデイ・チャイナタウン！」
Here we go. It's "Flyday Chinatown"!
It's so fly-day, fly-day chinatown
真夜中の人ごみに
in the midnight crowd.
It's so fly-day, fly-day chinatown
はじける ネオン サイン
the neon signs pop!
肩にぶつかる 外国人 ウインクを投げる
A foreigner throws a wink over my way,
知らん顔の あなた とまどいの ひ と コ マ
your face is struck with bewilderment.
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
真夜中の人込みに
In the midnight crowd
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
はじけるネオンサイン
The neon signs pop!
肩にぶつかる外国人（ジンガイ） ウイングを投げる
A foreigner throws a wink over my way
知らん顔のあなた とまどいのひとコマ
Your face is struck with bewilderment
踊り疲れていても 朝まで遊ぶわ
Even if I'm tired of dancing, I'll play along 'til the morning
港の見える場所で 何か飲みたいのよ
I'd like to drink something at the place where a harbor is seen
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
ジャスミンに接吻（くちづけ）を
A kiss of the jasmin
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I don't belong here either
お店にならぶ 繻子のドレスを指す
I point to the silk dress in the shop
渋い顔のあなた わがままがいいたい
With your silence, I think you're being selfish
愛想笑いのおじさん きっと似合うわと
Because of that smile, that dress surely suits me
どこか静かな場所で 着替えてみたいのよ
I'd let to go somewhere quiet
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
繻（しゅす）ざれの見月あかり
The moonlight hits my cheeks
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I don't belong here either
お店にならぶ 繻子のドレスを
I point to the silk dress in the shop
渋い顔のあなた わがままがいいたい
With your silence, I think you're being selfish
愛想笑いのおじさん きっと似合うわと
Because of that smile, that dress surely suits me
どこか静かな場所で 着替えてみたいのよ
I'd let to go somewhere quiet
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
繻（しゅす）ざれの見月あかり
The moonlight hits my cheeks
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I don't belong here either
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
真夜中の人込みに
In the midnight crowd
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
はじけるネオンサイン
The neon signs pop!
肩にぶつかる外国人 ウイングを投げる
A foreigner throws a wink over my way
知らん顔のあなた とまどいのひとコマ
Your face is struck with bewilderment
踊り疲れていても 朝まで遊ぶわ
Even if I'm tired of dancing, I'll play along 'til the morning
港の見える場所で 何か飲みたいのよ
I'd like to drink something at the place where a harbor is seen
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
ジャスミンに接吻を
A kiss of the jasmin
It's so Fly-Day, Fly-Day Chinatown
私も異国人ね
I don't belong here either
男のコになりたいのよ 私…
I want to be a boy sometimes...
星のハイウェイ バイク飛ばし海へ
Riding my bike to the ocean past the starry highway,
アイツの後を つけて行くのさ そして夢を聞きたい
I'll chase after them and ask about their dreams.
今日一日だけでいい リボンを解いて
Just for today, I'll untie my ribbon
男のコにさせてといて 朝まで一緒ね
and let me be a boy until morning.
だけどchance いつかchance 二人dance する時には
But when chance, whenever chance comes to dance,
ふいに女にもどるの…
I suddenly turn back into a girl...
男のコになりたいのよ なぜか…
I want to be a boy for some reason...
世界中を自由に旅したい
Traveling freely around the world.
バラを一輪 飾るスーツで
In a suit adorned with a single rose,
最後の日のキメるのね
making a statement on my final day.
今日一日だけでいい すべてを叶えて
Just for today, I want to fulfill all my wishes
女のコには見せない 素顔が見たいのよ
and see my true face that I never show to girls.
そしてchance いつかchance 二人dance する時には
And when chance, whenever chance comes to dance,
アイツ好みになりそう…
I'll probably become just like him...
Sweet couple pi! pi! woo be popple pi! pi!
今日一日だけでいい リボンを解いて
Just for today, I'll untie my ribbon
男のコにさせてといて 朝まで一緒ね
and let me be a boy until morning.
だけどchance いつかchance 二人dance する時には
But when chance, whenever chance comes to dance,
ふいに女にもどるの…
I suddenly turn back into a girl...
Sweet couple pi! pi! woo be popple pi! pi!
sweet couple, pi pi, woo be popple, pi pi
今日一日だけでもいい
Just for today is fine,
リボンを解いて
untie the ribbon,
男のコにさせてといて
let me be a boy,
朝まで 一緒ね
together until morning.
だけどchance いつかchance
But chance, someday chance,
二人dance する時には
when the two of us dance,
ふいに女に もどるの
suddenly I return to being a girl.
sweet couple, pi pi, woo be popple, pi pi
SWEET MEMORIES
[Title: SWEET MEMORIES]
なつかしい 痛みだわ
A familiar ache...
ずっと前に 忘れていた
I'd long since forgotten.
でも あなたを見たとき
But when I saw you,
時間だけ後戻りしたの
time turned back.
「幸福？」と聞かないで
"Are you happy?" don't ask me that,
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm no good at lying.
友達ならいるけれど
I have friends, of course,
あんなには燃えあがれなくて
but I can't burn with passion like before.
失った夢だけが 美しく見えるのは何故かしら
Why is it only the dreams we've lost look so beautiful?
過ぎ去った優しさも 今は
Even your kindness, long gone,
甘い記憶 sweet memories
is now a sweet memory, sweet memories.
sweet memories
Don't kiss me baby
we can never be
so don't add more pain
please don't hurt me again
i have spent so many nights thinking of you longing for your touch
i have once loved you so much
あの頃は 若すぎて
Back then, we were far too young,
悪戯に傷つけあった二人
hurting each other just for fun.
色褪せた悲しみも 今は
Now even the faded sorrow
遠い記憶 sweet memories
is a distant memory, sweet memories.
失った夢だけが
Only the lost dreams...
なつかしい痛みなの
A familiar ache...
ずずっと前に忘れていたの
I forgot all about it a while ago.
でもあなたを見たとき
But when I saw you,
時間だけ後戻りしたのね
I went back in time for a moment.
「幸福？」と聞かないで
Don't ask me if I'm happy.
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not good at lying.
友達ならいるけど
I have friends,
あんなには燃え上がれなくて
...
失った夢だけが
Why is it only the dreams we've lost
美しく見えるのは何故かしら
That seem so beautiful?
過ぎ去った優しさも今は
Now even your long-past kindness
甘い記憶 sweet memories
Is a sweet memory...
don't kiss me baby
we can never be
so don't add more pain
please don't hurt me again
i have spent so many nights
thinking of you longing for your touch
i have once loved you so much
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame TELEVISION
[Title: Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame Television]
素晴らしいわ！ソラ！
Brilliant, Sora!
今のパフォーマンスはエレガンスの極み
That was a masterclass in elegance!
まさにマスタークラスだったわね！私の心は未だにメロメロドキドキしてるわ！
My heart is still melting, dokidoki!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
みんなと一緒に歌えて、本当にSweetな時間でした！
It's always such sweet times singing with everyone!
たしかにSweetな時間 Sweetな思い出…
Sweet times, sweet memories...
そして愛らしいネリッサ・レイヴンクロフト！
And the lovely Nerissa Ravencroft!
あなたも今夜は最高に輝いてるわよ！
You look absolutely smashing tonight!
あらリズ お上手ね
Oh, Liz, you're such a flatterer!
舞台袖から見ていたけど
I was watching from the wings
ついつい一緒に口ずさんじゃったわ
and I couldn't stop humming along.
おっと！二人への質問があるの！
Oh, I have a question for you guys.
もし二人でユニットを組むとしたらどんな名前にする？
So if you two formed a unit, what would your name be?
80年代のチャートに載るような派手なやつをお願い！
Something flashy for the '80s charts!
うーん そうね…
Hmm, well...
私たち共通点があるわよね？「ブルー」とか！
We have something in common, don't we?
ブルー！
Blue!
そらさんは伝説的な存在で
You're kind of legendary...
私は悪魔…
I'm a demon.
それから…
Show me, too.
しょうめい…つー…そう！どうかしら？
So, how about...
「BLUE MEGAMISAMA」なんてどうかしら？
"BLUE MEGAMISAMA"?
「BLUE MEGAMISAMA」！
"BLUE MEGAMISAMA"!
いいね すごく気に入った！「BLUE MEGAMISAMA」
Oh, I like that! I like that a lot!
ビューティフル！クールだわ！
Beautiful, so cool!
そら もう一つ質問よ
Sora, here's a question for you.
あなたは誰もが認めるアイドルだけど
We all know you are an idol,
今夜はまるで映画スターみたい！
but tonight you look like a movie star.
映画スター！
A movie star!
もし80年代の映画に出るとしたら何がいいかしら？
Which '80s movie would you want to star in?
「E.T.」
E.T.!
E.T.
最高ね！すごくいいね！
Oh, that's a good one! That's a good one!
私が自転車を用意するから そらはカゴに乗ってね！
I'll get my bike and you can hop in my bike, yeah?
オーマイガー！
Oh my god!
ネリッサにも質問よ！
Nerissa, a question for you!
あなたはパワフルな声の持ち主だけど
You've got a powerful voice, yes.
80年代のパワフルなバンドでお気に入りは？
What is your favorite powerful band from the '80s?
パワフルと呼ぶかわからないけど…
I don't know if I call them powerful.
答えはわかってるでしょ？
You know the answer.
言う前に言っちゃうけど「The Smiths」よ！
Before I even say it, it's The Smiths.
そうね あなたをよく知る私には愚問だったわ！
Yeah, I'm onto you enough
でも素敵な答えよ！ありがとう！
that I already knew the answer.
オルライト！
All right.
さて 私は次のワイルドな曲の準備に行かなくちゃ！
Okay, I better get off and get ready
ワイルド！
for the next wild track. Yes, wild.
あとは二人に任せるわ！たらー loves たらー バイバーイ！
I'll leave you guys to it. Taras loves, taras! Bye-bye!
それでは
All right, then,
次の曲にいきましょう！
let's move on to the next song, darlings!
Run...
「コブラ」
Cobra!
Huzzah!
コブラ Lyrics: 冬杜花代子 Music: 大野雄二
[Title: Cobra / Lyrics: Kazuko Otowa / Music: Yuji Ohno]
街をつつむ midnight fog
Streets wrapped in midnight fog
孤独な silhouette 動きだせば
A lonely silhouette, once it starts to move
それはまぎれもなく ヤツさ
It's an elusive guy, you see
cobra leaving me blue
cobra missing you true
cobra only few memories, after you
背中 にまとい つく羽衣 は
The wings you wear upon your back
オトコ という 名の ものがたり
Are something that we call an "Autoco."
許される はず もない peace & love
There's no room for peace and love here.
コブラ
Cobra...
leaving me blue
Living you, blue...
コブラ
Cobra...
missing you true
わかってる
I know what you want,
ほしいんでしょ
don't you?
艶やかなこの唇
My alluring lips
惹き寄せる
drawing you in
息を吸うほどに甘い蜜
With sweet nectar that takes your breath away
わかってる
You know what you want,
ほしいんでしょ
don't you?
二度見するこの背中
My figure that has you mesmerized
汗ばむ街 一人歩けば
Walking alone on the streets
Peace & Love
空を泳ぐ人魚のように
Like a mermaid swimming in the sky
サイレント抑えた
Silencing the silent
バイオレンス
violence
息づくたび
With every breath I take
秘密ひとり
A secret, all alone
闇を歩く奴ら
Walking through the darkness
小悪魔
Little devil
Cobra
Only a few memories after you
A missing tune
Cobra, only a few memories after you
初めてに刻まれた
Carved into the very first time
あの日はロマンと呼ぶには
That day is too thick to be called romance
厚すぎてめぐり来る
As it comes spinning around
日数もない
With not even enough days
息絶えても独占狂で Crazy for you
Breathing my last, madly, crazy for you
形の見えない繋がりを
A connection whose shape cannot be seen
信じたい
I want to believe in
アイ・トゥ・アイ
Eye to eye
周りにいつも男たち取り巻いててnerve
Surrounded always by men surrounding her like nerve
まるで君はvenus
As if you were Venus
遂に起こしたmiracleさ
Finally a miracle happened
砂漠の中かから、見つけ出したjewel
Finding a jewel out of the desert
迎えに行くよ! どんな時も
I'll go pick you up! No matter what time
振り回されてもとことんcrazy for you
Completely crazy for you, no matter how pushed around
形の見えない繋がりを信じたい
I want to believe in a connection whose shape cannot be seen
eye to eye
時には確かめ合いたいよ!
Sometimes I want to confirm it with you!
don't you know, know, know...
it's love
小麦色した君の肌
Your wheat-colored skin
やたらそそるaction, 高すぎるよ! tension
An action that allures, tension is too high!
会えない夜は目の下に
On nights we can't meet, under my eyes
黒いenigmaがshadowを塗りにくる
A black enigma comes to paint the shadow
違う匂いじゃ、火がつかない
With a different scent, the fire won't catch
style, smile; まとめてmad about you
Style, smile; mad about you altogether
形の見えない繋がりで感じたい
I want to feel through a connection whose shape cannot be seen
heart to heart
時には確かめあわなきゃくちゃ
Sometimes we have to confirm it together
don't you know, know, know...
it's love
飾りのない素顔に戻る時
When returning to a plain, unadorned true face
弱さも見せて、俺だけに
Show your weaknesses and tears to me alone
離さない、離れない, このまらいつまでも
I won't let go, staying like this forever
時を重ねていこう
Let's accumulate time together
そしていつか come together
And someday come together
形の見えない繋がりを信じたい
I want to believe in a connection whose shape cannot be seen
eye to eye
時には確かめ合いたいよ!
Sometimes I want to confirm it with you!
don't you know, know, know...
it's love
形の見えない繋がりで感じたい
I want to feel through a connection whose shape cannot be seen
heart to heart
時には確かめあわなきゃくちゃ
Sometimes we have to confirm it together
don't you know, know, know...
it's love
隠せない愛しさが鬼のように戻る時
When hidden love returns like a demon
酔いさめも涙も見せておくだけに
Just showing my sobering up and tears
離さない離れないこのままいつまでも
Never letting go, never leaving, staying like this forever
時を重ねて行こう そしていつか come together
Let's pile up time and someday come together
形の見えない繋がりを
A connection whose shape cannot be seen
信じたい
I want to believe in
アイ・トゥ・アイ
Eye to eye
時には確かめ合いたいよ
Sometimes I want to confirm it!
Don't you know, don't you know
もしも願いが叶うなら 吐息を白いバラに変えて
If my wishes can be true, will you change my sighs to roses
逢えない日には部屋じゅうに 飾りましょう貴方を想いながら
Decorate them for you, thinkin' 'bout you every night
Darling, I want you 逢いたくて ときめく恋に走り出しそうなの
Darling, I want you, need to be with you, my heart craves for your love
Don't you know, don't you know, it's love
You are watching
ERB TV!
もしも願いが叶うなら 吐息を白いバラに変えて
If my wishes can be true, will you change my sighs to roses
逢えない日には部屋じゅうに 飾りましょう貴方を想いながら
Decorate them for you, thinkin' 'bout you every night
Darling, I want you 逢いたくて ときめく恋に走り出しそうなの
Darling, I want you, need to be with you, my heart craves for your love
迷子のように立ちすくむ わたしをすぐに届けたくて
Just like a lost child, standing here alone, by your side I want to be
ダイヤル回して手を止めた I'm just a woman Fall in love
I dialed the number, then stopped my hand. I'm just a woman, fall in love
If my wishes can be true Will you change my sighs
To roses, whiter roses Decorate them for you
Thinkin' 'bout you every night and find out where I am
I am not livin' in your heart
Darling, I need you どうしても 口に出せない願いがあるのよ
Darling, I need you so helpless I feel, deep inside I have a wish never to be said
土曜の夜と日曜の 貴方がいつも欲しいから
Want you, I need you, stay by my side, weekends won't go by without you on my mind
ダイヤル回して手を止めた I'm just a woman Fall in love
Can't stop you, can't hold you, can't wait no more. I'm just a woman, fall in love
Darling you love me 今すぐに
Darling, you love me, can't wait to hear
貴方の声が聞きたくなるのよ
Your voice and your words, need it now no later
両手で頬を押さえても 途方に暮れる夜が嫌い
Nights that I spend alone, thinking 'bout you here, peace is not with me
ダイヤル回して手を止めた I'm just a woman Fall in love
Can't stop you, can't hold you, can't wait no more. I'm just a woman, fall in love
Don't you remember When you were here
Without a thinking We were caught in fire
I've got a love song but Where it goes
もしも願いが叶うなら
If my wishes can be true...
吐息を白いバラに変えて
Will you change my sighs to roses?
貴方を想いながら
Thinkin' 'bout you every night...
Darling, I want you 逢いたくて
Darling, I want you...
ときめく恋に
Can't keep myself still,
駆け出しそうなの
my heart craves for your love.
迷子のように
Just like a lost child,
立ちすくむ
standing here alone.
わたしをすぐに
By your side I want to be,
届けたくて
as soon as it can be.
I'm just a woman Fall in love
...
青い水平線を いま駆け抜けてく
I'm running past the blue horizon now,
とぎすまされた 時の流れ感じて
keenly feeling the flow of time on me.
ときめきへと 動き出す世界は
Ah, the world gets going towards something thrilling,
忘れかけてた 遠い夢の訪れ
the coming of a distant dream I'd forgotten all about.
Ride On Time さまよう思いなら
Ride on time, take my wandering thoughts as they are...
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light my heart on fire.
あふれる喜びにもどがれ Ride On Time
Flood me with joy, ride on time.
僕の輝く未来 さあ回り始めて
C'mon, bright future of mine, start turning.
虚ろな日々も 全て愛に溶け込む
All these hollow days melt away into love.
何という朝 今すぐ君のもと
Ah, what a morning! I'm gonna go deliver my fired up heart to you,
届けに行こう 燃える心迷わぬよう
wherever you may be right now, with zero hesitation.
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy, oh.
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, I'll light my heart on fire.
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, ride on time.
...
届けに行こう 燃える心今こそ
I'm gonna go deliver my fired up heart to you right now, oh.
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright that it makes me dizzy, oh.
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, I'll light my heart on fire.
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, ride on time, oh.
...
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy, oh.
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, I'll light my heart on fire.
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, ride on time.
...
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy, oh.
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, I'll light my heart on fire.
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, ride on time.
...
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy, oh.
青い水平線を いま駆け抜けてく
I’m running past the blue horizon now
とぎすまされた 時の流れ感じて
Keenly feeling the flow of time on me
ときめきへと 動き出す世界は
Ah, the world gets going towards something thrilling
忘れかけてた 遠い夢の訪れ
The coming of a distant dream I’d forgotten all about
Ride On Time さまよおう想いなら
Ride on time, take my wandering thoughts as they are
やさしく受け取めて そっと包んで
And wrap them gently around yourself, oh
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, light my heart on fire
あふれる喜びにと 拡がり Ride On Time
Flood me with joy, ride on time
僕の輝く未来 さあ回り始め
C’mon, bright future of mine, start turning
虚ろな日々も全て愛に溶け込む
All these hollow days melt away into love
何という朝今すぐ君のもと 届けに行こう 燃える心迷わず
Ah, what a morning! I’m gonna go deliver my fired up heart to you
Ride On Time 時よ走り出せ
Ride on time, time, take off running!
愛よ光り出せ 目もくらむ程
Love, start shining! So bright you make me dizzy, oh
Ride On Time 心に火を点けて
Ride on time, I’ll light my heart on fire
飛び立つ魂に送るよ Ride On Time
And send it to your soaring soul, ride on time
You're watching ERB TV
アンビリバボー！ここは1980年代の高校のディスコかしら！
Unbelievable! Are we in a 1980s high school disco?!
ああ、ディスコディスコ！ yeah、ディスコ！
Oh, disco disco! Yeah, disco!
この制服似合ってる？
How do we look in these uniforms?
最高にキュートよ！
You both look super cute!
でも本当の疑問は世界がこの魅力に耐えられるかってことよ！見ている人全員の心を奪ったわね 私の心もね！
But the real question is: Is the world ready for such charm?! You've captured the very heart of everyone watching, even mine!
この髭ってもしかして本物？
Is this mustache real?
ちょっとちょっと！手を離して！
Hey, hey, hey! Hands off! Hands off!
これは最高級のエグゾーディアンの工芸品なんだから！
This here is top-tier Exodian craftsmanship!
でもみんなに「Mustache (髭)」な質問をさせて！
But I must ask you a mustache question!
ころね！あなたはタフなワンちゃんだって聞いてるわ！あなたとマリンならどっちが学校の番長になるかしら？
Korone! I heard you're a tough pup! Between you and Marine, who would be the school leader?
さあ！ころね、考えてこい！
Well, Korone, think about it!
オーケー、マリン、かかってこい！
Okay, Marine, bring it on!
レディースたちここは80年代よ 物事はダンスバトルで解決しましょう！
Ladies, this is the 80s! We settle things with a dance-off!
それじゃあ次の質問よ！ダンスバトルならどっちが勝つかしら？
Which leads me to my next question! Who would win in a dance battle?
もっとお喋りしたいけど私は行かなくちゃ！ころね、マリン次の曲を紹介してくれるかしら？
I'd love to stay and chat, but I gotta dash! Korone, Marine, will you introduce our next song?
よろしくね！それじゃあね！
Cheers, ladies! Let's go!
次の曲は何かな？エネルギッシュな曲と聞いてますよ！
Now, what's our next song? I hear it's a super energetic one!
よし、準備はいいみたいだね！
Alright, looks like everything's ready!
せーの、オラに元気をわけてくれ！
Ready, set, lend me your energy!
光る雲を突き抜け fly away
Piercing the shining clouds, I fly away
からだじゅうに広がる パノラマ
While a panorama spreads through my body.
顔を蹴られた地球が怒って 火山を爆発させる
Kicked in the face, the earth gets angry, and makes a volcano explode!
溶けた氷の中に恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
Within the melted polar ice, if there’s a dinosaur, I want to train it to balance on a ball!
cha-la head-cha-la
何が起きても気分はへのかっぱ
No matter what happens, I feel like it’s no big deal!
cha-la head-cha-la
胸がパチパチするほど騒ぐ元気玉... sparking!
Just as loudly as my heart pounds, the genki-dama roars... sparking!
空を急降下 jet coaster
Diving through the sky on a roller coaster
落ちてゆくよ パニックの楽園へ
I fall into a paradise of panic!
景色逆さになると愉快さ 山さえお尻に見える
The scenery turns upside-down and I cheer up, 'Cause the mountains even look like butts!
悩む時間はないよ どこかに潜む「ビックリ!」に逢いたいから
There’s no time for worrying, 'Cause there’s a surprise hidden somewhere, and I wanna find it!
cha-la head-cha-la
頭カラッポの方が夢詰め込める
I’d rather have my head be empty, so I can stuff it with dreams!
cha-la head-cha-la
笑顔ウルトラ z で 今日 も アイヤイヤイヤイ イヤイ イ . . . sparking !
With a smile that’s ultra-z, even today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai... sparking!
光る雲を突き抜け fly away
Piercing the shining clouds, fly away
(fly away)
からだじゅうに 広がる パノラマ
A panorama spreading through my body
顔を蹴られた地球が 怒って
Kicked in the face, the earth gets angry
(怒って)
(gets angry)
火山を爆発させる
And makes a volcano explode!
溶けた北極の中に
Within the melted polar ice,
恐竜がいたら 玉乗り仕込みたいね
if there's a dinosaur, I want to train it to balance on a ball!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きてても気分は へ へ へ の カッパ
No matter what happens, I feel like it's no big deal!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がピチピチするほど
Just as loudly as my heart pounds,
騒ぐ元気玉… Sparking!
the Genki-Dama roars... Sparking!
空を急降下 jet coaster (coaster)
Diving through the sky on a roller coaster (coaster)
落ちていくよ パニックの楽園へ
I fall into a paradise of panic!
景色逆さになると愉快さ (愉快さ)
The scenery turns upside-down and I cheer up (cheer up)
山さえ お尻に見える
'Cause the mountains even look like butts!
悩む時間はないよ
There's no time for worrying,
どこかに潜む 「ビックリ!」に逢いたいから
'cause there's a surprise hidden somewhere, and I wanna find it!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
頭 カラッポ の方が 夢 詰め込める
I'd rather have my head be empty, so I can stuff it with dreams!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
笑顔 ウルトラ Z で
With a smile that's ultra-Z,
今日も アイアイアイアイアイ…
even today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
何が起きてても気分は へ へ へ の カッパ
No matter what happens, I feel like it's no big deal!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がピチピチするほど
Just as loudly as my heart pounds,
騒ぐ元気玉… Sparking!
the Genki-Dama roars... Sparking!
CHA-LA HEAD-CHA-LA
胸がパチパチするほど 騒ぐ元気玉！
My heart is crackling so much, the Genki-Dama roars!
最高にイカしてるね！スタンディングオベーション！
Absolutely bonkers! Standing ovation!
この素晴らしいエネルギーに拍手を送るわ！
And round of applause for that spectacular energy!
MCデスクへようこそねえ！そしてリゼは！
We did it! Welcome to the desk, Nene and Iroha!
リゼー！
Rize!
リゼお誕生日おめでとう！
Happy birthday, Rize!
そうよ 今日は私の誕生日なの！
Oh, yes! It's my birthday!
リゼとってもパワフルだね！パワフルなダンスにパワフルな歌唱！
Rize, you're so powerful! Powerful dance and powerful singing!
そしてパワフルなポーズね！
And powerful poses!
そんでもってキュート！
And super cute!
私たちとってもパワフルだね！みんなとってもパワフルだったわ！
We're very powerful! Everyone was so powerful!
そうぜおちゃんイントロヘアー！金髪は最高にパワフルだわ！超サイヤ人みたいだね！
So CEO-chan, into blonde hair! Blonde hair is super powerful! Like a Super Saiyan!
超サイヤ人級のブロンドヘアーよ！最高にパワフル！最強ね！
Super Saiyan-level blonde hair, you know! Super powerful! The strongest!
みんなのパワーを感じたわ！ねえねえあなたのエネルギーはまるでドラゴンのようね！
I felt everyone's power! And Nene, your energy is like a dragon!
視聴者のみんなに最高にパワフルなドラゴンポーズを見せてくれる？
Could you show the viewers your most powerful dragon pose?
ドラゴンポーズ！ ガオーン！ ドラゴンマウス ガッチンガッチン パワフル！
Dragon pose! Roar! Dragon mouse clack-clack, powerful!
今のは最高だったわ！そしていろは！
That was incredible! And Iroha!
ダンス中のあなたの集中力は凄まじかったね！あなたの一番のサムライポーズを披露してくれる？
Your focus during that dance was amazing! Could you demonstrate your finest samurai warrior stance?
OK 見てて！拙者はサムライだよ！ ジャキーン！
OK, look! I'm a samurai! Shing!
強い！強い！侍だね！
Strong! Strong samurai!
今夜は大きなグループでパフォーマンスしたわね ステージには全部で七人もいたのよ！
You both performed in a big group tonight. There were seven of us all together on stage!
教えて欲しいんだけど リハーサル中に一番「チャラ（自由奔放）」だったのは誰？
Tell me, who was the most carefree member at rehearsals?
えっねえねえ先輩を指差してるの？リハーサル中もずっとそうだったよね！
Eh, are you pointing at Senpai? It was always like that during rehearsals too!
Congratulations! さようなら～！
Congratulations! Goodbye~!
みんなでやろう！ みんなで、あ…、あ、じゃあ次！
Let's all do it together! Ah, then next!
よし、じゃあオッケー！
Alright, okay!
せーの！ おめでとう！
Ready, set! Congratulations!
スタンディングオベーション！
Standing ovation!
いやーねえ！
Oh man!
ねね先輩が一番チャラいわ！ チャラチャラ！
Nene-senpai is the flashiest one! So flashy!
キュートでチャラい！最高だわ！ チャラチャラ！チャラチャラ！
Cute and flashy! The best! Flashy, flashy!
本当に素晴らしい時間だったね！
That was truly a wonderful time!
でも悲しいことに、次で最後の曲になっちゃうの。グランドフィナーレの準備をしなくちゃ！すぐに戻ってくるね、みんな！
But sadly, that brings us to our last song. I must prepare for the grand finale! I shall return very soon, gang!
ねね、いろは、少しの間観客のみんなを楽しませておいてね！
Nene, Iroha, please keep the audience entertained for a moment!
二人にお願いしたわよ！オッケー侍！また後でね！オッケー戦士！
I'll leave it to you two! Okay samurai! See you soon! Okay warriors!
バイバーイ！頑張ってねー！
Bye-bye! Do your best!
さあ、今夜のスターのリスは、一体最後に何を見せてくれるんでしょうか？
Now, what kind of final performance will tonight's star, Liz, show us...
ね、楽しみですね！じゃあ皆さん、見るのそのままです！それでは行きましょう！
We are so excited! Everyone, watch the stream as it is! Well then, let's go!
おい！ You are watching ERB TV！ せーの、ヒュッザー！
You are watching ERB TV! Ready, Huzzah!
I believe the morning sun
Always gonna shine again and
I believe a pot of gold
Waits at every rainbow's end
I believe in roses kissed with dew
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
I believe in make-believe
Fairy tales and lucky charms and
I believe in promises
Spoken as you cross your heart
I believe in skies forever blue
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' the way that I do
You can call me Pollyanna
Say I'm crazy as a loon
I believe in silver linings
And that's why I believe in you
I believe there'll come a day
Maybe it will be tomorrow
When the bluebird flies away
All we have to do is follow
I believe a dream can still come true
Why shouldn't I believe the same in you?
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' the way that I do
I believe in friends and laughter
And the wonders love can do
I believe in songs and magic
And that's why I believe in you
You may say I'm a fool
Feelin' this way about you
There's not much I can do
I'm gonna be this way my life through
'Cause I still believe in miracles
I swear I've seen a few
And the time will surely come
When you can see my point of view
I believe in second chances
And that's why I believe in you
ハロー、愛するみんな
Hello, sweethearts!
ラブリーで見つめて、見つめて…
Lovely to see you, to see you...
ラブリー！
Lovely!
ERB TVの初放送はどうだった？
What did you think of the first
show on ERB TV?
楽しんでくれたかしら？選曲はどう思った？
Did you enjoy it? What did you
think of the song choices?
素晴らしいゲストたちと一緒にパフォーマンスできて、私は本当に楽しかったわ
I really hope you loved it as much as
I love performing with such amazing guests!
Huzzah!
ロザリアンのみんな 準備はいい？
Rozarians, to arms!
Are you ready?
サプライズの準備はできてる？
For the surprise?
みんなに見せたい素敵なものがあるの
I have something lovely
to present to all of you!
いくわよ…
Here we go!
3… 2… 1…
3... 2... 1...
誕生記念グッズよ！
I have birthday merch!
まずはこちら
First up is this!
この誕生記念グッズの美しいキービジュアルがタペストリーになったわ！
The beautiful key visual art of this
birthday merch is on a tapestry!
ボビーとロザリアンと一緒にリラックスしているところなの
I'm relaxing with Bobby and a cute
Rozarian after a dance workout!
この素敵なレトロ風タペストリーを飾って写真を撮って私に見せてね！
Please display this wonderful retro-style tapestry
and take pictures for me to see, please!
みんながどんな風にお部屋に飾ってくれるかすごく楽しみだわ
Would absolutely love to see how you
decorate the room with it!
テレビスタジオに来てくれたんだから自分専用のERB TVマグカップも手に入れてね
As you visited the TV studio,
make sure to pick up your very own ERB TV mug!
テレビを見ながらこれで水分補給してね！
Use it to hydrate while
watching me on the tele!
「お母さん私ERB TVに出てるよ！」 「見て、テレビに出てるわ！」
"Mom, I'm on ERB TV!"
"Hey, mom, I'm on the tele!"
たぶん今頃クイーンマザーもテレビでこれを見てるわね
I go saying that and most likely right now
Queen Mother is watching this on the tele!
次はみんなも私も欲しがっていたもの…
Next, you've all been wanting this,
and so have I!
ロザリアンのぬいぐるみよ！
A Rozarian plushie!
超ハッピ～
I'm so freaking happy!
私の冒険は忠実で素晴らしいロザリアンのみんながいなければ成り立たなかった
My adventures have been nothing
without my loyal, amazing Rozarians!
これであなただけのブラッドフレイム王国の力強いロザリアンを飼えるわね
Now you can have your very own Rozarian
Bloodflame Kingdom powerful pooch!
私はあなたの剣 あなたは私の盾
I am your sword, and you are my shield!
私たちは一緒なら最強よ！
We are powerful together!
That's right!
次は激アツ ピンバッジ4個セットよ！
Next, we have a set
of four pin badges!
私がピンバッジ集めが大好きなのは知ってるわよね
Y'all know I love
collecting pin badges,
新しいコレクションに加えてね
and here's some new ones
for you to collect!
ERB TVロゴ シールド 肉球 そしてBFKヘッドバンドをしたロザリアンよ
We have the ERB TV logo badge, shield badge,
Rozarian paw, and a Rozarian with a headband on saying BFK!
レペゼン Blood Flame Kingdom
Blood Flame Kingdom, represent!
80年代風のヘッドバンドすごく似合ってるよ
You all look amazing with an
eighties headband on, I must say!
最後に英語と日本語の両方で新しいボイスパックを収録したわ
Lastly, I recorded another voice pack
in both English and Japanese!
ボイスパックのタイトルは「エリザベスと体操」
The voice pack is called
"Exercise with Elizabeth",
一緒に運動して私たちの修行に加わってね さらなる高みを目指すために…！
so join me on our training arc as we exercise
together, onwards and upwards!
フルセットを購入してくれた方にはフルセット購入特典があるわ！
Then, if you purchase the whole set, the
full shebang, there's a full set purchase bonus!
キービジュアルのポストカードがもらえるんだけどそれだけじゃないの
You get a postcard with the key
visual on it, but that's not all!
数量限定版には私の直筆サイン入りポストカードが入っているわ
The limited quantity includes a postcard with
a handwritten signature by yours truly!
限定版がなくなっても複製サイン入りのポストカードはもらえるからね
Please do not worry, even when those run out,
you still get the postcard with my replica signature!
以上が生誕グッズのフルセットでした！
And that is the full set
of my birthday merch!
どうだったかしら？
What do you think?
グッズには愛を込めたわ
There's been a lot of love
put into this merch,
特にロザリアンを抱っこするのが待ちきれない！
and especially can't wait to
cuddle my own Rozarian plushie!
ライブが終わる前にゲストのみんなに特別な感謝を伝えたいわ
Wow, before we wrap up, I'd like
to give a special thanks to the guests!
みんなと一緒にパフォーマンスできて光栄だったわ
It is an honor performing with you all!
この素敵な思い出をずっと大切にするわ
I'll treasure these
sweet memories forever!
スタッフのみんなも素晴らしい仕事をありがとう
Thank you to the crew,
amazing job everyone!
振り付けを考えてくれたダンスの先生たちもありがとう私のダンスでみんなを誇らしい気持ちにさせられたら嬉しいな
Thank you to my dance teachers who made
the choreos! I hope it made you proud!
そしてなによりもロザリアンのみんな 私の最初の誕生日ライブを見てくれて本当にありがとう
Most of all, thank you my beautiful kingdom,
my Rozarians, for checking out my birthday live!
ERB TVの初放送！
First ERB TV show!
最高の曲ばかりだったわよね？
Those were some bops
and a half, right?
美味しいものを食べて水分補給してしっかり寝るよ 私たちの王国を素晴らしく強く保ちたいからね
Okay, make sure to eat good noms, hydrate,
get good sleep to keep our kingdom strong!
みんなのことが大好き
I love you all very much!
そして何より私の声がみんなの力になりますように
And most of all, let my
voice be your strength!
ByeBye~